# Benjamin Boswick

Master of Landscape Architecture Candidate - M3 Student

A hard-working individual who effectively prioritizes tasks, operating in both independent and group settings. With intense dedication towards academics, a consistent work ethic is displayed. Keeping an open mind is necessary for creativity and retaining new information and experiences in the field.

## **Contact Information**

#### **Email**

ben.boswick@gmail.com

#### Website

https://boswick.design

## Education

2021/09 - M.L.Arch., University of Manitoba

<sup>2018/09 -</sup> B. Env.D., *University of Manitoba* 

<sup>2016/09</sup> - University 1/Faculty of Science, *University of Manitoba* <sup>2018/05</sup>

## Hard Skills

#### Microsoft Office

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Photoshop

**AutoCAD** 

Rhino3D

**TwinMotion** 

SketchUp

Adobe Illustrator

**VectorWorks** 

# Soft Skills

Communication

Collaboration

Interpersonal Skills

Time Management

Estimation

Dedication

**Problem Solving** 

Merchandising

## Experience

2015/02 - Sales Associate

McMunn and Yates Building Supplies (600 Pembina Highway)

- Created and managed sales orders through a Point of Sales system
- Developed quotes for various products and structural packages
- Direct customer service
- Tactful handling of challenging situations
- Attained knowledge of an array of products in every department
- Assembled merchandising displays
- Operated and maintained necessary machinery
- Provided ancillary services outside and off-site

## **Associations**

#### 2020-22 Student Mentor and Ambassador

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

- Providing advice and guidance to peers
- Participating as a faculty representative in various events

## <sup>2020-21</sup> Student Mentorship Program Cofounder

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Partners Program

- Coordinating student mentoring groups
- Ensuring success of participating mentors and mentees

### <sup>2020-21</sup> Graduation Committee Treasurer

University of Manitoba Faculty of Architecture Student Architecture Society

- Managing committee finances
- Communicating and maintaining faculty wear inventory

## <sup>2019-22</sup> Student Affiliate

Manitoba Association of Landscape Architects (MALA)

## Publications and Awards

- 2021-22 MALA/LASA Student Rendering 2022, (City-Wide Category, 2nd Place)
- 2020-21 "Hidden Communities", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 30 (Individual Project)
- 2020-21 "Choice-Less", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 30 (Individual Project)
- 2019-20 "Urban Orchard", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 29 (Individual Project)
- 2018-19 "Untitled", Warehouse Journal, Vol. 28 (Collaborative Project)